// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let Maths = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Her thinking leans ____ democracy.",
    answer: "(B) toward",
    options: [
      "(A) with",
      "(B) towards",
      "(C) for",
      "(D) None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "He got too tired _____ over work.",
    answer:  "(A) because of",
    options: [
      "(A) because of",
      "(B) because off",
      "(C) on",
      "(D) for"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "He crossed the broken bridge ____ warning.",
    answer:  "(A) in spite of",
    options: [
      "(A) in spite of",
      "(B) in spite off",
      "(C) on",
      "(D) about"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "_____ his principles, he has to be very careful.",
    answer:"(C) with regard to",
    options: [
      "(A) with regard of",
      "(B) with regard on",
      "(C) with regard to",
      "(D) None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Building has been built _____ the new plan.  ",
    answer:   "(B) in accordance with", 
    options: [
      "(A) accordance to",
      "(B) in accordance with",
      "(C) for",
      "(D) about"
    ]
  },
  {
      numb: 6,
      question:"The train ____ as fast as the bus.",
      answer: "(C) moves",
      options:[
        "(A) went",
        "(B) running",
        "(C) moves",
        "(D) going"
      ]
  },
 {
     numb: 7,
     question: "He was seen _____ to the school.",
     answer: "(a) irrational",
      options:[
        "(A) went",
        "(B) going",
        "(C) gone",
        "(D) go"
      ]
 },
 {
     numb: 8,
     question: "She ____ in the sun for 1 hour.",
     answer:  "(B) has been sitting",
     options:[
         "(A) sitting",
         "(B) has been sitting",
         "(C) has been sit",
         "(D) has sit"

     ]
 },
 {
    numb: 9,
     question: "____ it help you in your studies ?",
     answer:  "(b) 6",
     options:[
         "(A) will",
         "(B) was",
         "(C) is",
         "(D) are"

     ]
 },
 {
    numb: 10,
     question: "I ____ never seen such a picture before.",
     answer:  "(C) haves",
     options:[
         "(A) did",
         "(B) was",
         "(C) haves",
         "(D) has"

     ]
 }
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];